<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" version="2.0"><channel> <atom:id>tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-4891748495862422700</atom:id> <astBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 16:35:59 +0000</astBuildDate> <title>Ci Bech's Blog</title> <description>This is a description</description> <link>http://cibech.web.fc2.com/</link> <managingEditor>noreply@blogger.com</managingEditor> <generator>Blogger</generator> <openSearch:totalResults>2</openSearch:totalResults> <openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex> <openSearch:itemsPerPage>25</openSearch:itemsPerPage><item> <guid>200908030802132500000300</guid> <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate> <atom:updated>2009-08-03T08:02:00+00:00</atom:updated> <title>Test3</title> <description>Any depiction or recreation of real world locations, entities, businesses, or organizations is not intended to be or imply any sponsorship or endorsement of this game by such party or parties. Produced under license of Ferrari Spa. FERRARI</description> <link>http://localhost/cphpblog/showpost.php?pid=3</link> <author>Ci Bech</author></item><item> <guid>200907021722698500000200</guid> <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2009 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate> <atom:updated>2009-07-02T17:22:00+00:00</atom:updated> <title>Test2</title> <description>So where is the leader of the free world? President Obama has picked out a place for himself among the spectator seats. From there, speaking of and to Iran, he comments that "The world is watching." But while he has "deep concerns," especially about the violence he's been observing on television, he sees no gain in "meddling in Iranian elections."

A cynic might infer that Obama is simply waiting for the protesters to be cleared out of the way so he can carry on with his dreams of extending a hand to cut deals with the dissent-crushing, terror-drunk, uranium-loving godfathers of Tehran. More generously, one might wonder if Obama really believes Iran's people have the best chance of defanging their own despots if unarmed protesters and armed state security forces are left to hash out among themselves who's in charge.</description> <link>http://localhost/cphpblog/showpost.php?pid=2</link> <author>Ci Bech</author></item><item> <guid>200906021622132500000100</guid> <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2009 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate> <atom:updated>2009-06-02T16:21:00+00:00</atom:updated> <title>Test1</title> <description>With great courage, Iranians have been rising up against the tyranny of their 30-year-old Islamic Republic. This is a weak moment for Iran's terror-based regime, and democracies such as the U.S. should seize the chance to shake it further--and support the protesters in the process--by turning up the heat.</description> <link>http://localhost/cphpblog/showpost.php?pid=1</link> <author>Ci Bech</author></item></channel></rss>